

PERSONAL DETAILS

- +2348082666215
- utejoe.ju@gmail.com
- https://uyiobazeeportfolio.netlify.app

SKILLS

- Logical thinking
- · Software debugging
- Frontend: React, JS, CSS, HTML
- Backend: Node.js, Express.js,
 Django, Django REST Framework
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- DevOps: Render, Gunicorn, Pip, Collectstatic.
- Other: PHP, WordPress, REST APIs, Python, Authentication, State Management, LocalStorage

PROJECTS

- Music E-commerce App PHP + WordPress
- MERN E-commerce Website
- MERN Social Media App
- Al Event Recommendation Web App Django + JS + Tailwind
- Django Social media app
- Online University
- Currently building a Language learning school

REFERENCE

Engr. Nowamagbe Ogbeifun

MNSE, COREN Reg. NIHTE, MNICE

Phone: +2347038645748

Email: nowamagbe.ogbeifun@uniben.edu

Uyi Obazee

Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

Experienced Full-Stack Software Engineer with 5 years of experience. Web Developement, MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, PHP, Wordpress, Python, Git, MySQL, Linux, and Bash scripting, software development methodologies, and database management systems. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work effectively in a teambased environment.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BEMA

Software Engineer | 2022 - 2024

- Built the Backend and part of the frontend development of a music website
- using PHP, WordPress, JavaScript, Python, HTML, and CSS.
- Established synchronization among our website database, an Ecommerce
- platform, and Mailerlite for our CRM by developing a custom WordPress plugin
- utilizing PHP and REST API.
- Integrated Wavesurfer library for interactive audio visualization in the website's
- footer.
- Established seamless connections to Easy Digital Downloads for efficient music
- · transactions.
- Integrated MailerLite API to facilitate seamless newsletter communication with
- users, enhancing the efficiency of email marketing processes.

FREELANCER/ REMOTE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Versatile Software Engineer | 2020-2022/2024-present

 Built and delivered full-stack web apps for clients using React, Node.js, and Django, PHP.

EDUCATION

Civil Engineering

University of Benin | 2018 - 2023

Software Engineering

AFRICA LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE 2022/23